https://batman-on-film.com/batman-on-film-coms-privacy-policy/

1960s BATMAN TV Series
BATMAN: THE MOVIE (1966)
BATMAN: RETURN OF THE CAPED CRUSADERS
BATMAN VS. TWO FACE
ANIMATED BATMAN TV
BATMAN WITH ROBIN, THE BOY WONDER (1968-1969)
THE NEW ADVENTURES OF BATMAN (1977)
BATMAN: THE ANIMATED SERIES
BTAS EPISODE REVIEWS
BATMAN BEYOND (1999-2001)
THE BATMAN (2004-2008)
BATMAN: THE BRAVE AND THE BOLD (2008-2011)
BEWARE THE BATMAN (2013-2014)
BATMAN HISTORY
BATMAN (Character Bio)
ANIMATED BATMAN MOVIES
MASK OF THE PHANTASM (1993)
SUBZERO (1998)
BATMAN BEYOND: RETURN OF THE JOKER (2000)
SCOOBY DOO MEETS BATMAN (2002)
BATMAN: MYSTERY OF THE BATWOMAN (2003)
THE BATMAN VS. DRACULA (2005)
BATMAN: UNDER THE RED HOOD (2010)
BATMAN: YEAR ONE (2011)
THE DARK KNIGHT RETURNS (2012/2013)
THE KILLING JOKE (2016)
THE LEGO BATMAN MOVIE (2017)
SCOOBY DOO & BATMAN: THE BRAVE & THE BOLD (2018)
BATMAN: GOTHAM BY GASLIGHT (2018)
BATMAN NINJA (2018)
BATMAN VS. TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES (2019)
BATMAN: HUSH (2019)
THE BATMAN & BATMAN AND ROBIN – The 1940s Serials
BATMAN (1966)
BATMAN (1989)
BATMAN ’89 Features on BOF
BATMAN RETURNS (1992)
BATMAN FOREVER (1995)
BATMAN & ROBIN (1997)
THE DARK KNIGHT TRILOGY (2005-2012)
BATMAN v SUPERMAN (2016)
JUSTICE LEAGUE (2017)
1960s BATMAN TV Series
BATMAN: THE MOVIE (1966)
BATMAN: RETURN OF THE CAPED CRUSADERS
BATMAN VS. TWO FACE
ANIMATED BATMAN TV
BATMAN WITH ROBIN, THE BOY WONDER (1968-1969)
THE NEW ADVENTURES OF BATMAN (1977)
BATMAN: THE ANIMATED SERIES
BTAS EPISODE REVIEWS
BATMAN BEYOND (1999-2001)
THE BATMAN (2004-2008)
BATMAN: THE BRAVE AND THE BOLD (2008-2011)
BEWARE THE BATMAN (2013-2014)
BATMAN HISTORY
BATMAN (Character Bio)
ANIMATED BATMAN MOVIES
MASK OF THE PHANTASM (1993)
SUBZERO (1998)
BATMAN BEYOND: RETURN OF THE JOKER (2000)
SCOOBY DOO MEETS BATMAN (2002)
BATMAN: MYSTERY OF THE BATWOMAN (2003)
THE BATMAN VS. DRACULA (2005)
BATMAN: UNDER THE RED HOOD (2010)
BATMAN: YEAR ONE (2011)
THE DARK KNIGHT RETURNS (2012/2013)
THE KILLING JOKE (2016)
THE LEGO BATMAN MOVIE (2017)
SCOOBY DOO & BATMAN: THE BRAVE & THE BOLD (2018)
BATMAN: GOTHAM BY GASLIGHT (2018)
BATMAN NINJA (2018)
BATMAN VS. TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES (2019)
BATMAN: HUSH (2019)
THE BATMAN & BATMAN AND ROBIN – The 1940s Serials
BATMAN (1966)
BATMAN (1989)
BATMAN ’89 Features on BOF
BATMAN RETURNS (1992)
BATMAN FOREVER (1995)
BATMAN & ROBIN (1997)
THE DARK KNIGHT TRILOGY (2005-2012)
BATMAN v SUPERMAN (2016)
JUSTICE LEAGUE (2017)
Batman-On-Film.com’s Privacy Policy
It is Batman on Film’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to https://www.batman-on-film.com (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “https://www.batman-on-film.com”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.
This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Batman on Film collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Batman on Film’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Batman on Film’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Batman on Film may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Batman on Film also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://www.batman-on-film.com blog posts. Batman on Film only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Batman on Film’s websites choose to interact with Batman on Film in ways that require Batman on Film to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Batman on Film gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at https://www.batman-on-film.com to provide a username and email address.
Advertisements
Batman on Film doesn’t not use cookies.  However, ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Batman on Film and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Links To External Sites
Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.
Cookies
To enrich and perfect your online experience, Batman on Film uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Batman on Film uses cookies to help Batman on Film identify and track visitors, their usage of https://www.batman-on-film.com, and their website access preferences. Batman on Film visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Batman on Film’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Batman on Film’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Batman on Film’s use of cookies.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Batman on Film may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Batman on Film’s sole discretion. Batman on Film encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Op-Out Information
If you would like to opt-out, please visit NAI’s opt-out page where you can learn more about NAI members who deliver tailored online ads and your choices to opt-out of receiving them.  CLICK HERE for more info.
Contact Information
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email.
FOLLOW BOF ON SOCIAL MEDIAFollow @batmanonfilm
SUPPORT BOF
TEAM BOFBill "Jett" Ramey1058 POSTS0 COMMENTShttps://batman-on-film.comTeam BOF341 POSTS0 COMMENTSPeter Verra100 POSTS0 COMMENTSRyan Lower88 POSTS0 COMMENTSJohn Bierly49 POSTS0 COMMENTShttp://www.johnbierly.com/Garret Grev43 POSTS0 COMMENTShttps://whataretheoddsffb.com/Ryan Hoss36 POSTS0 COMMENTShttp://www.smbmovie.com/Rick Shew33 POSTS0 COMMENTSEric Holzmann10 POSTS0 COMMENTSJavier Trujillo6 POSTS0 COMMENTSChris Clow4 POSTS0 COMMENTShttps://www.bychrisclow.com/BATMAN PODCAST NETWORK
/
ABOUT USFounded in 1998 by Bill "Jett" Ramey, BATMAN ON FILM
is the Net's longest-running Batman movie website.
Authoritative. Definitive. The Dadgum ORIGINAL!
Read BOF's PRIVACY POLICIY.Contact us: jett@batman-on-film.comFOLLOW US
BATMAN ON FILM © 1998-present Bill Ramey, all rights reserved. BATMAN" and all related characters and elements are the trademarks of and © DC Comics. BOF's PRIVACY POLICIY.
